the most recent indictment against Raul Castro, because US-backed planes tried to violate Cuban airspace,
not once, not twice, but many times, and eventually Cuban people had it up and shot it down,
which the Americans would do in a heartbeat, but now Raul Castro is being indicted.
So the Cubans have given so much to Africa, Algerian independence, Algerian liberation,
the Congolese, Che Guevara famously went to Congo after Patrice Lumumba was martyred.
They didn't have to do all this. They could have said, rightfully so, in some people's eyes,
we've got enough on our plate. Every couple of months, they try to assassinate our leaders,
but despite all of that, and then we've got the doctors during the COVID pandemic, the Ebola.
You know, to send your doctors into Ebola-stricken areas is something that no other country does,
but Cuba does it.